Finding Aid for Mary P. Sinclair papers, 1967-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Citizen Groups 1970-1996
  - League Against Nuclear Dangers (LAND) (WI), 3 folders (Box 7)
  - League of Conservation Voters (Washington, DC) 1976 (Box 7)
  - League of Women Voters (Midland, MI) 1969-1976, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Michigan Association of Conservation Ecologists (MACE) (Cereseo, MI) 1971-1973 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Council of Churches (Lansing, MI) 1973-1974 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Energy Conservation Group (MECOG; Lansing) 1977 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Lung Association (Lansing, MI) 1974-1975 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Science Teachers Association (Lansing, MI) 1974 (Box 7)
  - Michigan State Medical Society 1975 (Box 7)
  - Michigan Student Environmental Confederation (Lansing, MI) 1973-1977 (Box 7)
  - Mobilization for Survival (Philadelphia, PA) 1979 (Box 7)
  - National Committee to Stop Environmental Pollution (Washington, DC) 1970-1973 (Box 7)
  - National Intervenors, 10 folders (Box 7)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) (Midland, MI) 1975 (Box 8)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (NRDC) (Washington, DC) (Box 8)
  - New England Coalition on Nuclear Pollution, Inc. (Brattleboro, VT) 1973-1980 (Box 8)
  - No Nukes Conference (Chicago, IL) 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Northern Environmental Council (Duluth, MN) 1974-1976 (Box 8)
  - Northwest Michigan Energy Action 1978 (Box 8)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Services (NIRS) (Washington, DC) 1978-1980 (Box 8)
  - Nuclear Opponents Publication (Allendale, NJ) 1974-1978 (Box 8)
  - Port Huron Intervention Petition (Greenwood Energy Center, MI) 1974 (Box 8)
  - Potomac Alliance (Washington, DC) 1978 (Box 8)
  - Public Interest Research Group (PIRG) (ME, MA, VT) 1974-1977 (Box 8)
  - Public Interest Research Group in Michigan (PIRGIM) 1973-1980, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Public Media Center (San Francisco, CA) undated (Box 8)
  - RAIN Newsletter (Portland, OR) 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Safe Energy Alliance (Midland, MI) 1979 (Box 8)
  - Saginaw Intervenors (Midland, MI) 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Saginaw Valley Nuclear Study Group (Midland, MI)
    - Organization 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Saginaw Valley Nuclear Study Group (Midland, MI) (cont.)
    - Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box 8)
    - News releases 1970-1973 (Box 8)
    - Expenses 1970-1973 (Box 8)
    - Study undated (Box 8)
    - Newsletters 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Save the Dunes Council (Munster, IN) 1976 (Box 8)
  - Self-Reliance (Washington, DC) 1976 (Box 8)
  - Sierra Club
    - City Care Conference Detroit 1979 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence 1970-1978, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - International; 1972-1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - McCloskey, Michael comments to Am. Nuclear Society (Box 8)
    - Members (Box 8)
    - Minutes and Memos (Box 8)
    - Midland (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Murthy, K.K. (Box 8)
    - National Energy Policy Committee 1974 (Box 8)
    - National Energy Policy Committee Strip Mine Report (Box 8)
    - Newsletters (Box 8)
    - Nuclear Pamphlet 1974 (Box 8)
    - Resolutions (Box 9)
    - Watts Paper 1976 (Box 9)
    - World Energy Conference Detroit 1974 (Box 9)
  - Soil and Health Foundation 1973-1974 (Box 9)
  - Task Force Against Nuclear Pollution (Moorestown, NJ) 1973-1976 (Box 9)
  - Union or Concerned Scientists (Cambridge, MA) 1972-1978, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - United for Survival (Benton Harbor, MI) 1974-1976 (Box 9)
  - Valley Alliance (Kalamazoo, MI) 1980 (Box 9)
  - Watch on the AEC (Washington, DC) 1970-1974 (Box 9)
  - West Michigan Environmental Action Council (Grand Rapids, MI) 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Philadelphia, PA) 1973-1977 (Box 9)
  - Citizen groups (miscellaneous)
    - Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Michigan (Box 9)
    - Midwest (Box 9)
    - Not Michigan (Box 9)
    - Newspapers (Box 9)
  - Citizen Groups--Michigan 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Citizen Groups--Not Michigan 1989-1990 (Box 28)
  - Bay County Citizen Air Pollution Investigating Committee of the Saginaw Valley Region of the Michigan Lung Association, re: Karn-Weadock Plant 1976 (Box 28)
  - Citizens Clearinghouse for Hazardous Wastes, Inc. 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Citizens' Energy Project--Intelligence and Surveillance 1981 (Box 28)
  - Citizens' Utility Board, Madison, WI 1992 (Box 28)
  - Coalition for a Nuclear Free Great Lakes 1986 (Box 28)
  - Committee for Nuclear Responsibility 1970-1977 (Box 28)
  - Don't Waste Michigan
    - Big Rock 1984-1997 (Box 28)
    - Bylaws and Resolutions 1990-1994 (Box 28)
    - Corrosion consultant Rudolf Hausler's report re: VSC-24 nuclear waste cask 1996-1997 (Box 28)
    - General Correspondence 1989-1995 (Box 28)
    - Incorporation papers and mission statement 1994-1996 (Box 28)
    - Membership lists undated (Box 28)
    - Minutes 1993-1998 (Box 28)
    - Newsletters 1993-1994 (Box 28)
    - NRC Response to March 24, 1998 letter (Box 28)
    - Palisades Plant 1990 (Box 28)
    - Press Releases re: Low Level Nuclear Waste 1987-1988 (Box 28)
    - Printed materials (Box 28)
  - Ecology Center, Ann Arbor, MI 1995-1996 (Box 28)
    (Tracey Easthope)
  - Environmental Action Foundation, "Power Line, " 1977 (Box 28)
  - Environmental Policy Institute 1984 (Box 28)
  - Environmentalists for Full Employment circa 1977 (Box 28)
  - Government Accountability Project 1982-1989, 5 folders (Box 28)
    (Billie Pirner Garde)
  - Great Lakes Health Banner Project 1993 (Box 28)
    (Mary Ann Stroup)
  - International Nuclear Opponents 1985 (Box 28)
  - Lake Michigan Federation 1979 (Box 28)
  - Lake Michigan Federation--Dry Cask Storage 1992-1994 (Box 28)
  - Lone Tree Council
    - General 1979 (Box 28)
    - Newsletters 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Publicity materials 1979 (Box 28)
  - Michigan Activists re: Dow/NRDC Project 1996 (Box 29)
    (Linda Greer)
  - Michigan Citizens Against Toxic Substances 1987-1992, 2 folders (Box 29)
    (Kimberly Dunbar. Campaign against Envotech waste dump in Augusta twp., Washtenaw Co., MI)
  - Michigan Citizens Lobby 1985 (Box 29)
  - Michigan Consumers' Council 1984-1985 (Box 29)
  - Michigan State Medical Society: Policy on Air Quality 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - National Association for the Education of Young Children: Concerned Educators Allied for a Safe Environment (CEASE) 1981-1982 (Box 29)
  - National Audubon Society Energy Plan 1984 (Box 29)
  - National Campaign Against Toxic Hazards 1985 (Box 29)
  - National Network on Low Level Nuclear Waste Disposal 1988 (Box 29)
  - Networking Institute 1983 (Box 29)
  - New York Public Interest Research Center 1982 (Box 29)
    (James L. Murphy)
  - Northern Michigan Medical Society--Resolution on Nuclear Plants undated (Box 29)
  - Nuclear Information and Resources Service (NIRS) 1983-1985 (Box 29)
  - NIRS Teaching Materials 1982 (Box 29)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility 1981 (Box 29)
  - Plenty 1979 (Box 29)
  - Pollution and Environmental Problems, Inc. 1982-1983 (Box 29)
  - Public Citizen 1985 (Box 29)
  - Public Health Student Association, University of Michigan 1979 (Box 29)
  - Public Interest Research Group at University of Michigan 1981 (Box 29)
  - Rocky Mountain Institute: Amory B. Lovins 1984 (Box 29)
  - Safe Energy Coalition Campaign 1982-1984 (Box 29)
  - Saginaw County Medical Society, "Nuclear Energy," 1971 (Box 29)
  - Saginaw Valley Nuclear Study Group, Funding by Sierra Club and Michigan Audubon Society 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - Saginaw Valley Nuclear Study Group, Funding by Sierra Club 1980-1984 (Box 29)
  - Sierra Club, Publications re: Nuclear Energy 1981-1984 (Box 29)
  - Sierra Club Foundation, Grants and Expenses 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Sierra Club National Energy Committee 1979-1993, 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Sinnissippi Alliance for the Environment 1983 (Box 29)
  - Solar Lobby 1981-1983 (Box 29)
  - Toledo Coalition for Safe Energy: 2.206 petition re Dry Cask Storage 1997 (Box 29)
    (Alice Hirt, Terry Lodge, Charlene Johnson)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists 1979-1985 (Box 29)
  - United Church of Christ, Michigan Conference, Grants and Expenses 1979-1985 (Box 29)
- Great Lakes Energy Alliance (GLEA) 1978-1985
  The Great Lakes Energy Alliance files (1.0 lin. ft.) contain organizational records, such as membership lists, publicity and minutes and topical files relating to the group's involvement in specific events, such as the licensing hearings for the Fermi II nuclear plant. The periodic update reports that Sinclair sent to her grant funders at the CS Fund and the Children's fund (including repeated correspondence with Maryanne Mott) give a clear and contemporaneous picture of Sinclair's goals and objectives.
  - Correspondence 1978-1980, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Attorney General meeting September, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Big Rock 14 (Box 9)
  - Clergy letters (Box 9)
  - Constitution and by-laws (Box 9)
  - Drake, Gerald and Martha (Box 9)
  - Drey, L. (Box 9)
  - Economics (Box 9)
  - Evacuation (Box 9)
  - Fermi II (R. Bailey) (Box 9)
  - Fermi II (Lawsuit and petition to intervene) (Box 9)
  - Fundraising, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Group Information (Box 9)
  - Hearings (Box 9)
  - Kennedy Square rally (Box 9)
  - Legislators and lobbying (Box 9)
  - LeTarte, Helen (Box 9)
  - Letters to the editor (Box 9)
  - Lone Tree Council (Box 9)
  - Mailing lists (Box 10)
  - Meetings, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Michigan Coalition for Utility Reform (Box 10)
  - Michigan Coalition on Utilities and Energy (Box 10)
  - Michigan Energy Coalition (Box 10)
  - MUSE-Grant proposal (Box 10)
  - Newsletter, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Nuclear Information and Resource Service (Box 10)
  - Petitions (Box 10)
  - PIRGIM (Box 10)
  - Programs (Box 10)
  - Public Service Commission (Bill of Rights) (Box 10)
  - Press Releases January-February, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Resolutions (Box 10)
  - Safe Energy Alliance of Midland (Box 10)
  - USC-Grant proposal (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous (including cassette "Nuclear Power in Michigan") (Box 10)
  - Citizen Group Addresses undated (Box 30)
  - Fermi II 1985 (Box 30)
    (Jennifer E. Puntenney)
  - Funding, C.S. Fund 1984 (Box 30)
  - Funding, Office of Electric Utility 1979-1980 (Box 30)
  - Funding, Youth Project 1979-1984, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Membership undated (Box 30)
  - Organization Activities 1978-1982, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Talkers Handbook undated (Box 30)
- University of Michigan 1969-1985
  Materials in the University of Michigan series (1.4 lin. ft.) relate to Sinclair's work as a graduate student and lecturer. She received her MS in environmental communications in 1973 and a PhD at the School of Natural Resources in 1991. Syllabi, class work and correspondence with her professors may be found here. Her theses, however, are located in the Writing and Speeches Series. She held the position of lecturer from 1974 to 1978. Lecture materials and papers from conferences she attended in relation to this role are found in this series.
  - General file
    - Appointment as lecturer (Box 10)
    - Bentley Historical Library 1970-1985 (Box 10)
    - Bibliography and resume (Box 10)
    - Board of Regents (Box 10)
    - Courses attended
      - Fall 1974 (Box 10)
      - University course 315 (Box 10)
      - Bryant, Bunyan "Social Change: Energy and Land Ethics" 1979 (Box 10)
      - Porter, W., "Society and Mass Media: Journalism 700," 1969 (Box 10)
      - Sandman, Peter, "Mass Media and the Environment," 1973 (Box 10)
      - Communicating science (Box 10)
      - Mini-course (Conservation) (Box 10)
      - Notes and outlines (Box 10)
    - Environmental Advocacy Newsletters (Box 10)
    - Graduate school (Box 10)
    - Pigeon River Country Association (Box 10)
    - Residential College (Box 10)
    - Seminar June 25-29, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Statement of intent for doctoral program (Box 10)
    - Washington trip (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Teaching materials
    - Citizen action (Box 10)
    - Communicating science (Box 10)
    - Communicating science, notes) (Box 10)
    - Conservation (Box 10)
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Dilemmas of Progress in Energy (Box 10)
    - ECO (Box 10)
    - Energy (Box 10)
    - Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA) (Box 10)
    - Fermi (Box 10)
    - Hazards (Box 10)
    - Initiatives (Box 10)
    - Kikuchi, C. (correspondence) (Box 10)
    - Media (Box 10)
    - Michigan Moratorium (Box 10)
    - Midland hearings (Box 10)
    - Nuclear Option Conference (Box 10)
    - Nuclear plants (Box 10)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 11)
    - Radiation waste disposal (Box 11)
    - Sabotage (Box 11)
    - Sinclair studies (Box 11)
    - Thesis (first section) (Box 11)
    - University of Minnesota (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Conferences
    - Nuclear Option Conference October 17, 1975
      - Backgrounders and press releases, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Correspondence and publicity, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Funding (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous papers and clippings (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - Energy Conservation Conference November 1-2, 1977
      - Grant proposal (Box 11)
      - Letters (Box 11)
      - Presentations, 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Reactions to conference (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
- Government Agencies 1968-1978
  The Government Agencies files (1.6 lin. ft.) represent Sinclair's work with governmental regulators. The materials include government reports, correspondence, articles and legal pleadings. They are arranged into subseries for Federal, Regional, State and Local governmental bodies, and one for Legislation. This series contains only documents from the first accession. For the later time period, a researcher should look to the Topical Files series to locate information about government agencies.
  - Federal
    - Army Engineer District (Environmental Statements) 1974-1975
      - St. Joseph Harbor (Box 11)
      - South Haven Harbor (Box 11)
    - Atomic Energy Commission
      - Documents 1970-1971 (Box 11)
      - Environmental Considerations 1969-1973, 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Light water reactors (Generic problems) 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Rules and regulations 1967-1971 (Box 11)
      - Turbine missiles 1978 (Box 11)
    - Council on Environmental Quality Hearing 1975-1976 (Box 11)
    - Energy Research and Development Administration
      - Budget hearings 1975, 3 folders (Box 11)
      - Austin E. Heller speech November 3, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Plans for nuclear power 1976 (Box 11)
    - Federal Communications Commission 1974 (Box 11)
    - Federal Power Commission 1971
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy
      - Hearings and correspondence 1972-1974, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission
      - Correspondence 1975-1977 (Box 11)
      - Light water reactors (Generic problems) 1975 (Box 11)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority 1975 (Box 11)
  - Regional
    - Great Lakes Basin Commission
      - Correspondence 1970-1972 (Box 12)
      - Reports on energy facility siting 1976 (Box 12)
      - Water resources Study 1975 (Box 12)
      - General 1971-1976, 4 folders (Box 12)
  - State
    - Air Pollution Control Commission 1971 (Box 13)
    - Attorney General 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Department of Commerce 1977 (Box 13)
    - Department of Natural Resources 1974-1976
      - Natural Resources Commission 1970
        - Meetings 1968-1971 (Box 13)
        - Statements on nuclear power
          - 1974 (Box 13)
          - 1975 (draft) (Box 13)
          - 1976 (Box 13)
      - Solid Waste Management Act rules
        - Hearings 1979 (Box 13)
      - Water Resources Commission
        - Correspondence 1970 with SVNSG (Box 13)
        - Hearings 1970 on waste disposal (Box 13)
        - Hearings 1970 AEC response (Box 13)
        - Waste disposal 1976 (Box 13)
    - Department of Public Health 1971-1975 (Box 13)
    - Environmental Review Board (Box 13)
    - Legislature
      - Special Joint Committee on Nuclear Energy Report on incidents at Nuclear power plants 1979 (Box 13)
      - Nuclear Power Pollution Subcommittee
        - Nuclear plant safety
          - Testimony 1974 of Romano Salvatori (Box 13)
    - Public Service Commission
      - Correspondence 1972-1974 (Box 13)
      - Consumers Power Company (Box 13)
      - Nuclear plant decommissioning petition (Box 13)
      - Hearing on nuclear power moratorium October 24, 1974 (Box 13)
      - Hearing: references for Mary Sinclair's testimony October 24, 1974, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - Intervention (Box 13)
      - Meeting August 17, 1978 (Box 13)
      - Testimony by Mary Sinclair December 3, 1969 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Local
    - East Central Michigan Planning and Development Commission 1977 (Box 13)
    - East Central Michigan Planning and Development Region (Box 13)
    - Midland County Commissioners 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Municipalities (Michigan Public Power Association) 1977 (Box 13)
  - Legislation
    - Legislation 1974-1979 (Box 13)
- Midland Plant, NRC hearings 1970-1983
  The Midland Plant, NRC hearings series (6.4 lin. ft.) documents the ongoing battle of Sinclair and her compatriots against unsafe conditions at the Midland Nuclear Power Plant. The materials in the first accession (boxes 13-16) are presented as they were received, and are in chronological order. Materials from several simultaneous legal actions, correspondence and research materials are mixed together in these files. They comprise the "Chronological" subseries.
  The later accession for this series (boxes 30-34) contains substantial chronological overlap and probable duplication with the first accession, but the materials are separated according to genre. The "General" subseries includes correspondence, research, clippings and reports and is arranged alphabetically. The "Pleadings and Orders" subseries and the "Transcripts" subseries are arranged chronologically. The transcripts contained in this last series are voluminous documents which represent verbatim accounts of evidentiary hearings.
  - Chronological
    - November, 1970 petitions to intervene (Box 13)
    - April, 1973 (Box 13)
    - November-December, 1973
      - 1973-1974 Show-cause hearings (Box 13)
    - September, 1976
      - Aymond, A. H., 2 folders (Box 13)
    - October, 1976 (Box 13)
    - November, 1976
      - Response of Consumers Power and Dow Chemical (Box 13)
      - Meeting with Consumers Power (notes) (Box 13)
      - Oreffice, Paul (testimony) (Box 13)
      - Reports (Box 13)
      - Temple's memo (Box 13)
      - News stories (Box 14)
      - News conference December 30, 1976 (backgrounder) (Box 14)
      - Testimony, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - December, 1976
      - Transcripts of NRC hearings December 1-3, 1976, 3 volumes (Box 14)
      - News clippings (Box 14)
      - Aymond, A. H., remarks to New York Society of Security Analysts December 22, 1976 (Box 14)
      - Transcript of NRC hearings December 14, 1976, 1 volumes (Box 14)
    - January, 1977
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 5 folders (Box 14)
      - Briefs and interrogatories (Box 14)
      - Press releases and clippings (Box 14)
      - Transcript of NRC hearings January 19, 1977, 1 volumes (Box 14)
    - February, 1977
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 3 folders (Box 14)
      - Funding intervenors, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Financial statement of need (Box 14)
      - Myron Cherry's brief (Box 15)
      - News clippings (Box 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - March, 1977
      - Papers, re. NRC hearings, 5 folders (Box 15)
      - Letters to Congress and President (Box 15)
      - Senator Edward Kennedy letter on funding citizens' groups (Box 15)
      - Dow Chemical, N-plant cost estimate) (Box 15)
    - April, 1977
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - May, 1977
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - June, 1977
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 5 folders (Box 15)
    - July, 1977
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - August, 1977 (Box 15)
    - September, 1977 (Box 15)
    - October, 1977 (Box 15)
    - November, 1977 (Box 15)
    - December, 1977 (Box 15)
    - January, 1978 (Box 15)
    - February, 1978 (Box 15)
    - March, 1978 (Box 15)
    - November, 1978 (Box 15)
    - May, 1980
      - Papers re. NRC hearings (Box 15)
      - Technical reports
        - "Investigation of Preservice Failure of Midland RPV Anchor Studs" (Box 15)
        - "Acceptability for Service of Midland RPV Anchor Studs" (Box 15)
    - June, 1980
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - July, 1980
      - Papers re. NRC hearings, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - August, 1980 (Box 16)
  - General Topics
    - Advisory Committee for Reactor Safeguards (ACRS) 1981-1982, 1988 (Box 30)
    - Anderson, Dr. C.M.: Expert Witness undated (Box 30)
    - Cracks in Unit I 1983 (Box 30)
    - Marshall, Wendall--Intervenor 1982-1983 (Box 30)
    - Operating License Hearing 1979-1984 (Box 30)
    - Suspension hearings documents (Box 30)
  - Environmental Statements
    - Final Environmental Statement January 1977 (Box 30)
    - Final Supplement to the Final Environmental Statement related to the Construction of Midland Plant Units 1 and 2 June 1977 (Box 30)
    - Draft Environmental Statement related to the operation of Midland Plant Units 1 and 2 February 1982 (Box 30)
    - Comments on Draft Environmental Statement April 1982 (Box 30)
    - Final Environmental Statement Related to the Operation of Midland Plant Units 1 and 2 July 1982 (Box 30)
  - Pleadings and Orders
    - Decision February 14, 1978 (Box 30)
    - Order Modifying Construction Permits December 6, 1979 (Box 30)
    - NRC Staff Motion for Summary Disposition April 14, 1981, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Decision of Atomic Safety Licensing Board (ASLB)--14 NRC1768 December 22, 1981 (Box 31)
    - Exceptions to Partial Initial Decision (Remand Proceeding) Dated December 22, 1981-February 22, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Intervenor Stamiris' Supplemental Findings of Facts and Conclusions of Law March 29, 1982, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Saginaw Nuclear Study Group's Motion to Strike Dow's March 22, 1982; Brief and NRC Staff's Response, April 1982 (Box 31)
    - Notice of Violation April 21, 1982 (Box 31)
    - ASLB Order April 30, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Contentions of Intervenor Mary P. Sinclair June 1982, December 1982 (Box 31)
    - Impact of Table S.3 Case (Aeschliman v. NRC), September-November 1982 (Box 31)
    - Decision of ASLB September 9, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Response by Mary Sinclair for Production of Documents September 27, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Notice of Violation February 8, 1983, February 18, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Motion to Reconsider Order Upholding Attorney-Client Privilege Protection for November 24, 1982; Consumers-Bechtel Meeting, August 12, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Cross Reference to Previously Filed Findings of Fact January 27, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Motion to Request the Caseload Forecast Panel to Evaluate the Consumers Power Co. New Construction Completion Date for the Midland Nuclear Power Plant April 19, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Statements for Meeting of NRC re: Midland Plant. April 28, 1984 (Box 31)
      (Tom Hearron, Chair of Lone Tree Council; John D. Selby, Chair, President and CEO Consumers Power; Barbara G. Stamiris, Intervenor; and Billie Garde, Government Accountability Project)
    - Stamiris' 2nd Supplemental Proposed Findings of Fact May 11, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Reply to Stamiris' 2nd Supplemental Proposed Findings of Fact June 22, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Motion to Cancel Operating License October 24, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Applicant's Response to Intervenor Stamiris' Pleading of December 24, 1984-February 8, 1985 (Box 31)
    - Pleadings and Orders undated (Box 31)
  - Transcripts
    - Paul Oreffice Testimony, NRC, Chicago February 2, 1977 (Box 31)
    - Oral Argument, NRC, Chicago November 17, 1977 (Box 31)